Guide to the Robert Steck Papers ALBA.104
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: General
  - Prago, Albert: on Jewish Participation in Spanish Civil War ( The Shekel article), Oct 1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Prago, Albert: on Spanish Women Political Prisoners (pamphlet), undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "Raisin in the Sun": Investment, Apr 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Reed, Bob, undated, Mar 1982-Mar 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Robinson, Earl, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Robinson, Edward (Frenchy), May 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Rosen, Alex, undated, Apr 1968-Jul 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Rosenstein, Herman, Jun 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Ross, Adolph (Buster), undated, Dec 1984-Mar 1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, undated, Feb 1980-Mar 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Ryan, James G.: "The American Communist Party and the Spanish Civil War" (research paper), Jun 1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Salzman, Salman: Israel Association of Volunteers of the International Brigade in Spain, Oct 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Sandburg, Carl, Jan 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Saroff, Sophie, undated, Nov 1974-Apr 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Saroff, Sophie: 80th Birthday Celebration, undated, Feb 1976-May 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Saroff, Sophie: 80th Birthday Celebration: Correspondence, undated, Dec 1975-May 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Saroff, Sophie: 80th Birthday Celebration: Script and Speeches, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Schappes, Morris: on Israel/Palestine Conflict, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Schappes, Morris: Jewish Currents, Aug 1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Segal, Edith, 1973-1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Senior Outreach Advocacy Program, Sep 1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Smith, Randall Pete, undated, Apr 1977-Aug 1981 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Society for Spanish and Portuguese Historians, undated, May 1977 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Spain: Gellhorn, Martha: "The Indomitable Losers: Spain Revisited", Feb 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Spain: List of Slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Spain: Politics and Government after the Spanish Civil War: Articles, undated, 1938, Sep 1969-Mar 1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Spain: Politics: Notes, undated, May 1981 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Spain: Return Trips to, undated, Jan 1977-Dec 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Spain: Suarez, Manny, Feb 1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Spain: Women Political Prisoners in the 1970s, undated, Apr 1970 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Spain: Workers Commission: Camacho, Marielino, Oct 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Spanish Civil War: "African Americans and the Spanish Civil War" (chapter), undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Spanish Civil War: African-American Volunteer List, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Spanish Civil War: Article: "Liberacion" (Costa Rica), Sep 1937 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Spanish Civil War: Articles on, undated, Sep 1936-Dec 1938 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Spanish Civil War: Articles on, undated, Mar 1970-Sep 1987 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Spanish Civil War: Bibliographies and Readings, undated, Nov 1987 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Spanish Civil War: Booklet Compiled from Clippings: "The Americans are Coming!", ca.1938 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Spanish Civil War: Booklet Compiled from Clippings: "Save Me, I Am Too Young to Die!", ca.1938 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Spanish Civil War: City College Veterans, undated, Dec 1979-Apr 1980 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Spanish Civil War: "The Crime of Guernica" (pamphlet), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Spanish Civil War: Dr. Seymour J. Robbins Memorial Concert, Mar 1938 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Spanish Civil War: Embargo against Spain, undated, May 1938-Jan 1939 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Spanish Civil War: Erika Mann: German and Austrian Veterans, Mar 1939-May 1939 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Spanish Civil War: Films: "A Valley in Spain" (proposal), Aug 1983 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Spanish Civil War: Films: "Between the Wars—The Spanish Civil War", Jul 1978 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Spanish Civil War: Films: General, undated, Jan 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Spanish Civil War: Films: "The Good Fight", undated, Nov 1978-Nov 1995 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Spanish Civil War: Finnish-American Veterans, Aug 1992 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Spanish Civil War: General, undated, May 1944 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Spanish Civil War: Graphic Propaganda (photocopies), ca.1937 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Spanish Civil War Historical Society: General, undated, Jan 1980-Jun 1982 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Spanish Civil War Historical Society: Monument to American Vets in Spain, May 1982-Apr 1987 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Spanish Civil War: International Brigades, Oct 1986 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Spanish Civil War: Irish Participation, Aug 1980 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Spanish Civil War: "Jews and General Franco", undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Spanish Civil War: Karol (Walter) Swierczewski: Russian Veteran, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Spanish Civil War: Latin-American Volunteers, Aug 1979 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Spanish Civil War: League of American Writers and American Students Union, ca.1938 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Spanish Civil War: MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion of Canada, May 1978-Mar 1982 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Spanish Civil War: "Memories of Spain" Concert: on Board R.M.S. Ausonia, Dec 1938 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Spanish Civil War: New York University Students in, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Spanish Civil War: Poetry, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Spanish Civil War: Puerto Rican Participation, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Spanish Civil War: "Reflections on the Spanish Civil War" ( Monthly Review article), Sep 1962 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Spanish Civil War: Sam Katz: German Veteran, Dec 1986 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Spanish Civil War: Stephen Hegarty: Foster Parents' Plan for Children in Spain (photocopies), Mar 1939-Apr 1939 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Spanish Civil War: Streisand Peace Memorial, Dec 1937 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Spanish Civil War: Swiss Veterans, undated, Oct 1976-Jan 1986 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Spanish Civil War: Time Magazine Coverage (photocopy), Jul 1936-Mar 1939 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Spanish Civil War: U.S. Medical Participation, Jul 1990-Aug 1990 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans: Articles on, undated, Feb 1975-May 1994 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans: Politics, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans: Questionnaire, undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Spanish Civil War: Voice of the Federation: Letters to the Editor (photocopies), 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, undated, Oct 1946, Sep 1980 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Steck: to Al Prago on Jewish Identity, Zionism and the Middle East, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Steck: Alfred E. Smith High School, undated, Nov 1968-Nov 1976 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Steck: Biographical, undated, Mar 1986-Feb 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Steck: to Carl Geiser on Soviet Union, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Steck: Employment Recommendations, Oct 1942-Jun 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Steck: with George Watt on Nazi-Soviet Pact, POUM, Orwell, Anarchists, Mar 1983-Jan 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Steck: Housatonic Valley Regional High School, undated, Jul 1970-Jun 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Steck: Interview Release, Feb 1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Steck: on Jewish Identity, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Steck: Medical History, Jan 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Steck: Oral History Interview Transcript, Sep 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Steck: P.S. 30, undated, Jan 1968-May 1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Steck: Regional Board of Education, Jan 1993-Aug 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Steck: School and Community Activities, undated, Sep 1968-Apr 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Steck: School of Foreign Service, Georgetown University, Nov 1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Steck: School Transcripts, 1941-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Steck: Speaking Engagements, undated, Dec 1987-Feb 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Steck: Student Evaluations and Work, undated, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Steck: Student Evaluations: "Contemporary Problems", 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Steck: Taconic Learning Center/Housatonic Youth Service Bureau, undated, Feb 1989-Jun 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Steck: Teacher Retirement, Nov 1971-Jun 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Steck: Teaching: Certificates and Diplomas, 1968-1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Steck: Teaching: Notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Steck: Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Great Valley, AZ, Dec 1996-Mar 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Steck: West Side High School, undated, Apr 1976-Jun 1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - VALB: 32nd Anniversary, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - VALB: 40th Anniversary, May 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - VALB: 40th Anniversary (script by Steck), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - VALB: 42nd Anniversary, Feb 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - VALB: 45th Anniversary, Apr 1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - VALB: 47th Anniversary, Apr 1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - VALB: 50th Anniversary, undated, Sep 1985-Oct 1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - VALB: 51st Anniversary, Apr 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - VALB: 54th Anniversary, Apr 1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - VALB: 55th Anniversary: Dr. Charlie Clements (speech), Apr 1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - VALB: Bay Area Post, Oct 1979-Feb 1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - VALB: Constitution and By-Laws, 1939, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - VALB: Correspondence, undated, Mar 1976-Jun 1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - VALB: Dinner (Steck remarks), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - VALB: Finances, undated, Jan 1978-Dec 1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - VALB: General, undated, Sep 1976-Aug 1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - VALB: Historical Commission, undated, Jan 1968-Mar 1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - VALB: Meeting Minutes and Notes, undated, 1969-May-93 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - VALB: Memorial Services, undated, Nov 1982 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - VALB: New York Post, Nov 1976-Jun 1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - VALB: Oral History Project, undated, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - VALB: Polish Jewish Volunteers: Controversy, undated, Feb 1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - VALB: Subversive Activities Control Act and Legal Activity, May 1980 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - VALB: Tour of Spain, Oct 1986 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - VALB: Veterans Rights Committee, undated, Feb 1980-May 1982 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Ware, Marianne, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Watt, George: "Another Look at the Good Fight" (speech), Dec 1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Watt, George: "Is There 'No Experience of History' for Us?" (article), Jan 1988 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Weissman, Irving, undated, Jul 1979-Feb 1988 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Wellman, Saul, undated, Sep 1978-Sep 1979 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Wellman, Saul: on Santiago Carrillo Visit to Yale University, undated, Dec 1977 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Wiesel, Elie, Feb 1986 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Wolff, Frieda, undated, Feb 1983 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Wolff, Milton, undated, Jul 1979-Apr 1988 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - World War II: Camp Ritchie: Military Intelligence Training Center, Nov 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - World War II: Camp Ritchie: Military Intelligence Training Center: Certificate of Completion, December 23, 1944 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS006)
  - World War II: Demobilization Papers, Jun 1944-Nov 1947 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - World War II: Kesler Field, MS, Dec 1945 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - World War II: Officers Candidate School, Apr 1944-Aug 1944 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Writings: "Camp Coop" partial drafts, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Writings: Eulogies, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Writings: "Homeless", undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Writings: Lectures: "The American Dream", undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Writings: Lectures: Mark Twain, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Writings: Lectures: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Writings: Letters to the Editor and Drafts of Articles, undated, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Writings: Miscellaneous, undated, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Writings: on POUM, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Writings: Poetry, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Writings: "Re: San Pedro", undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Writings: Script Drafts, undated, ca.1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Writings: Speeches and Presentations, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Yates, James, undated, May 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Series II: Prisoners of the Good Fight
  - Subseries II:A: Biographical Files
    - Abello, Pete, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Acken, Edgar L., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Adolphe, Hans, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Alvarez, Manuel Eddy, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Alvarez y Gonzalez, Bernardo, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Amades, Vincent Sanches, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Anderson, Ray, undated, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Andreason, Alf, undated, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Argirakis, Matthew, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Assa, Alberto, undated, Aug 1938-Oct 1938, Jan 1983-Mar 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Babsky, Sidney, undated, Sep 1979-Feb 1982 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Balagurchik, Elias (Ilya), undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Barr, Charles, undated, ca.1939 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Barr, Reuben (Conrad Henry Stojewa), undated, Dec 1939-Feb 1940, May 1979-Jun 1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Beamud, Antonio, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Belau, Carl, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Berman, Leopold, undated, May 1978 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Bertolini, Renato, May 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Blackman, Frank, Apr 1979 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Blair, John Clarence Avie, undated, Jul 1976-May 1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Braley, Roger, undated, May 1978 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Brown, Tom, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Browne, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Burns, Paul, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Cameron, James, Feb 1979-Oct 1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Canales, Victor Gerro, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - de la Casa, Jesus Andrew, undated, Jul 1979-Oct 1979 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - de la Casa, Jose Manuel, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Chang, Jul 1979 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Chase, Homer, undated, Nov 1979-Mar 1985 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Chase, Van Rensalar, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Clemente Garcia, Santos, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Colver, Robert, undated, Sep 1979 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Company, Manuel, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Conway, Morris Michael, undated, Jun 1940 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Dahl, Harold (Whitey), undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Delgado Delgado, Carmelo, undated, Jul 1937, Jul 1985 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Delgado, Emilio, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Delitch, George, undated, Aug 1939, Feb 1982 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Domnauer, Olaf, undated, May 1980-Aug 1980 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Doran, Dave, undated, Jun 1938 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Doran, Lawrence Fant, undated, ca.1939 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Dorland, Norman, undated, 1942-1956, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Doyle, Bob, Jan 1983-Jun 1983 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Dykstra, Matthew, undated, Apr 1979 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Earl, Howard, undated, Jun 1982 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Eggar, Dougal, undated, Aug 1983 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Fajardo, Marcos, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Firmin, John Charles, undated, Jul 1980-Aug 1980 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Freed, Edward Milton, undated, Apr 1937-1938, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Garafolo, Patrick J., undated, Jun 1979-Feb 1982 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Garcia, Enrique, undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Geiser, Carl, undated, May 1937-Oct 1938, Feb 1979-Jun 1983 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Gerhardt, Julius, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Gilbert, Tony, Sep 1981 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Giler, Henry, undated, Feb 1974-Feb 1982 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Goddard, Howard, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Grachow, Leo, undated, 1928, Nov 1974-Feb 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Grant, Samuel, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Grant, Walter Fairbanks: Correspondence regarding (photocopy), Oct 1939 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Grant, Walter Fairbanks: Correspondence regarding, undated, Jan 1980-Dec 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Grant, Walter Fairbanks: Drafts of Pamphlet on: I, ca.1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Grant, Walter Fairbanks: Drafts of Pamphlet on: II, ca.1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Grant, Walter Fairbanks: Notes and Articles, undated, Feb 1980-Jul 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Grant, Walter Fairbanks: Publication of Pamphlet on, undated, May 1982-Sep 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Grant, Walter Fairbanks: Spanish Civil War Correspondence from and Other Writings by, Oct 1929-Feb 1937 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Grigas, Joseph, undated, May 1939, May 1978-Dec 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Grodski, Frank, undated, Jun 1956, Apr 1979-Jun 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Gurko, Maurice, undated, Aug 1979-Sep 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hafner, Otto, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Hall, Charles, undated, Jan 1977-Jun 1980, Oct 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Hathaway, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Hausman, Carl, undated, Aug 1937-Oct 1938 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Heinricher, Stanley, undated, May 1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Heinzman, Georg, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Higgins, John, undated, Apr 1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Hodge, Edward, undated, Feb 1979-May 1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Jacobs, Edward Deyo, undated, Aug 1979-Jun 1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Jenkins, John Hollis, undated, Dec 1978-Feb 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Johnson, Edward, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Jones, Tom, Aug 1981-Oct 1982 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Jordan, Heinz, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Keeler, Addison Stan, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Keith, Charles, undated, Feb 1939, Jun 1978-Jul 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Keller, Fred, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Kelly, David Gillis, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Kerhlicker, Anthony Peter, undated, Jun 1939, Jun 1979-Jul 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Kleiman, Harry (Cohn Haber), undated, Jun 1979-Sep 1979 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Koneski, Samuel, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Kormes, Karl, Sep 1983-May 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Kunstlich, Alexander Cecil, undated, Jan 1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Lardner, James Phillips, undated, Jan 1979-Nov 1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Leiserowitz, Sol: Letters from S.S. Manhattan, Paris and Spain, Jul 1938-Mar 1939 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Leiserowitz, Sol: Miscellaneous, undated, Jun 1917, 1935-1950 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Leiserowitz, Sol: Miscellaneous, undated, Jun 1982-Aug 1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Lemke, Otto, undated, Apr 1979-Jan 1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Lerner, Sol, undated, Jun 1979-Feb 1982 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Levitas, Maurice, Aug 1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Lewis, J.F., undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Listhaeghe, Gustav, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Loesch, Karl, Jul 1981 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Logan, John Monroe, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Mail, Jack, undated, Jul 1979-Oct 1982 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Maki, Martin, undated, Jan 1973-Jan 1983 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - McCartney, Garry, Mar 1983-Mar 1984 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - McEachron, Paul, undated, Jul 1979 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Megquier, Henry Ben, undated, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Merriman, Robert, undated, Mar 1979-Apr 1986 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Miller, Fred Ralph, undated, Dec 1978 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Miller, William Colfax, undated, Jan 1980-Apr 1983 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Montanarella, Felice, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Moon, Jimmy, undated, 1938, May 1978-Aug 1981 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Moskowitz, Ignatz, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Neafus, Ralph, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Neri, Dino, undated, Feb 1979-May 1979 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Opara, Rudolph, undated, Jun 1979 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Ornitz, Louis Noah, undated, Aug 1978-Nov 1983 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Paivio, Julies, Nov 1977 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Pannszewicz, John Peter, undated, Sep 1979-Mar 1983 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Parker, Max, undated, Apr 1938, Jun 1979-Dec 1983 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Parks, John, undated, Mar 1979-Nov 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Polansky, Samuel, undated, Jan 1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Poling, Eugene, undated, 1937-1939, Nov 1973-Mar 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Pringle, Claude, undated, Mar 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Raacke, Peter, undated, May 1978-Mar 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Radacoy, Joseph, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Riffe, Herman Carl, undated, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Robles, Francisco Coco, undated, Aug 1939 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Romer, Samuel and Edna, undated, Jan 1979-Feb 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Rosenblatt, Sidney, undated, Feb 1939-Nov 1944, Nov 1978-Jun 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Rutherford, James, undated, Feb 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Ryan, Frank, undated, Apr 1979-May 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Sanjenis, Cabarrocas (Sergio), undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Shufer, Max, undated, Feb 1979-Nov 1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Shields, Art, undated, Jun 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stanley, Fred (Tex), undated, Apr 1979-Jul 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Steck, Robert, undated, Jul 1938-Jan 1940 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Steck, Robert, undated, Jan 1976-Jan 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Steinberg, Jack, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Stern, Marvin, Mar 1937 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Stevenson, Alwyn, undated, May 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Stix, Frederick, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Stone, William, undated, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Streit, Herman, Jul 1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Tabb, Herbert (Hy), undated, Dec 1978-Feb 1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Tenor, Leon, undated, Mar 1939, Oct 1978-Jan 1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Thayer, Donald, undated, Jun 1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Thompson, Richard Chester, undated, Jun 1978-Feb 1983 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Ticer, Leon Norwell, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Tobman, Morris (Moishe), undated, Sep 1939, Dec 1978-May 1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Torgoff, Leo, 1936-1939 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Torgoff, Leo, undated, Jan 1982-Oct 1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Wallach, Hy, undated, Dec 1939, Nov 1979-Jun 1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Weinand, Robert, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - West, Frank, Sep 1981 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Young, Joseph, undated, Sep 1978-Dec 1983 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Zarth, Alfred, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Ziegler, Albert, undated, Jan 1932-Dec 1938 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Ziegler, Albert, Jan 1939-Jul 1940 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Ziegler, Albert, undated, Jan 1982-Jul 1985 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Biographical Materials: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Biographical Materials: Miscellaneous: Alvarez – Busch, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Biographical Materials: Miscellaneous: Camnitz – Fernandez, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Biographical Materials: Miscellaneous: Garcia – Kruisement, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Biographical Materials: Miscellaneous: Lamas -- Nunez, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Biographical Materials: Miscellaneous: O'Beirne – Small, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Biographical Materials: Miscellaneous: Smith – Zdananskas, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Biographical Summaries, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Subseries II:B: Subject Files
    - American Ex-Prisoners of War, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Archivo Parroquial del Carcedo de Burgos, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Articles re: Prisoners, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Articles re: Prisoners, undated, Apr 1980-Sep 1980 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Belafonte, Harry: Fundraiser, undated, Feb 1981-May 1981 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Bibliographies and Sources, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - British Prisoners, Nov 1982 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Carney, William: Visit to San Pedro de Cardena, undated, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Committee for the Release of International Prisoners in Spain, Dec 1939 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Consultants and Acknowledgements, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)